A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25 FA368
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Public Relations File, 1; 59 Cubic Feet
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1115)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1116)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1117)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1118)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1119)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1120)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1121)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1122)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1123)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1124)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1125)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1126)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1127)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1128)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1129)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1130)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1131)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1132)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1133)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1134)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1135)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1136)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1137)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1138)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1139)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1140)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1141)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1142)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1143)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1144)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1145)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1146)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1147)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1148)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1149)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1150)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1151)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1152)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1153)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1154)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1155)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1156)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1157)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1158)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1159)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1160)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1161)
  - May 31, 1972 - September 28, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1162)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1163)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1164)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1165)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1166)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1167)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1168)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1169)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1170)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1171)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1172)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1173)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1174)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1175)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1176)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1177)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1178)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1179)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1180)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1181)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1182)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1183)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1184)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1185)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1186)
  - September 29, 1972 - November 22, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1187)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1188)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1189)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1190)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1191)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1192)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1193)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1194)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1195)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1196)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1197)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1198)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1199)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1200)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1201)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1202)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1203)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1204)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1205)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1206)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1207)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1208)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1209)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1210)
  - November 22, 1972 - February 18, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1211)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1212)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1213)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1214)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1215)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1216)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1217)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1218)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1219)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1220)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1221)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1222)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1223)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1224)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1225)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1226)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1227)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1228)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1229)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1230)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1231)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1232)
  - February 21, 1973 - July 7, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1233)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1234)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1235)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1236)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1237)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1238)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1239)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1240)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1241)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1242)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1243)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1244)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1245)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1246)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1247)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1248)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1249)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1250)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1251)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1252)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1253)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1254)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1255)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1256)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1257)
  - July 7, 1973 - November 14, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1258)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1259)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1260)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1261)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1262)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1263)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1264)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1265)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1266)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1267)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1268)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1269)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1270)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1271)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1272)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1273)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1274)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1275)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1276)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1277)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1278)
  - November 15, 1973 - October 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1279)
  - Index, 1958-1973 (Box 59, Folder 1280)
- Latin American Mission, 1969; 2; 1.6 Cubic Feet
  Subseries 2 is arranged chronologically.
  Subseries 2 is a collection of daily releases issued during Rockefeller's Presidential Mission to Latin America in 1969. At the request of President Richard M. Nixon, Rockefeller consulted with the leaders of 20 Latin American republics to solicit their opinion concerning U.S. inter-American policies and to determine the needs and conditions of the countries. The visits were made over the course of four separate trips. The bulk of the material in this subseries is transcripts of Rockefeller's speeches delivered during the trips. Also included are lists and resumes of the 36 advisors of the Governor's testimony on his findings and recommendations before the House Subcommittee on Inter-American Affairs and the Senate Subcommittee on Western Hemisphere Affairs.
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1281)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1282)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1283)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1284)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1285)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1286)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1287)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1288)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1289)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1290)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1291)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1292)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1293)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1294)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1295)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1296)
  - April 30, 1969 - November 12, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1297)
  - November 12, 1969, November 24, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1298)
  - November 12, 1969, November 24, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1299)
  - November 12, 1969, November 24, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1300)
  - November 12, 1969, November 24, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1301)
  - November 12, 1969, November 24, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1302)
  - November 12, 1969, November 24, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1303)
- Agency and Commission Reports, 3; 13.5 Cubic Feet
  These reports are arranged chronologically by the date of their release to the press.
  Subseries 3 is a collection of 371 reports issued by New York State agencies and commissions. Related press releases are filed with many of the reports. These reports were presumably filed in the Press Office so that the Press Office staff could prepare press releases for them and could answer questions from the public concerning the report or related programs.
  - New York Republican State Committee Yearbook, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 1304)
  - Summary of Reports, May-June; 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1305)
  - Purcell Report re: Railroad & Bus Line Problems in New York State, May 12, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1306)
  - Task Force on Middle Income Housing, June 6, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1307)
  - Task Force on Middle Income Housing, June 6, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1308)
  - Special Task Force on Protection from Radioactive Fallout, July 7, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1309)
  - Summary of Studies Initiated by NAR, October 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1310)
  - Interdepartmental Committee on Traffic Safety, November 23, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1311)
  - Proposed Reorganization of the Executive Branch of New York State Government, December 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1312)
  - Taxation of Non-Residents of New York State, December 2, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1313)
  - Taxation of Non-Residents of New York State, December 2, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1314)
  - Public Works Stockpile Program, December 23, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1315)
  - Task on Youth & Juvenile Delinquency, December 23, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1316)
  - Local Government Legislation, December 28, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1317)
  - Simplification of Income Tax Statute, December 29, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 1318)
  - State Relations with New York City, 1934-1960 (Box 61, Folder 1319)
  - Review of the Parole System of New York State, January 2, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1320)
  - Report on Power Resources, January 3, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1321)
  - Special Problems Respecting Charitable Solicitations, January 25, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1322)
  - Investigation of Railroad Full Crew Laws, January 26, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1323)
  - Commission on Governmental Operations of New York City, Interim Report, February 1, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1324)
  - Municipal Police Training Council, February 5, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1325)
  - Radioactive Fallout Report, February 18, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1326)
  - Radioactive Fallout Report, February 18, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1327)
  - Committee on Hospital & Medical Care, February 29, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1328)
  - Committee on Investment of Public Pension Funds, March 3, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1329)
  - Milk Licensing, March 14, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1330)
  - Tax Structure Study Committee, Interim Report, June 22, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1331)
  - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 1332)
    Annual Report, June 30, 1960
  - Higher Education, January 15, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1333)
  - The Added Years, Report on Aging, November 28, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1334)
  - New York State Committee Annual Yearbook, 1960, December 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1335)
  - Albany: Plan For the Capital City, December 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1336)
  - Economic Expansion in New York State, December 21, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1337)
  - Governor's Council on Rehabilitation, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1338)
    Annual Report, December 22, 1960
  - New York City General Business & Financial Tax, December 28, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1339)
  - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, December 29, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1340)
  - Atomic Energy Report, December 30, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1341)
  - Summary of Reports, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 1342)
  - Investigation of Law Enforcement in Buffalo, January 1961 (Box 62, Folder 1343)
  - Study of Public Welfare Administration in New York State, January 25, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 1344)
  - Study of Public Welfare Administration in New York State, January 25, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 1345)
  - Study of Public Welfare Administration in New York State, January 25, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 1346)
  - McKinsey Report on State Salaries, January 26, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1347)
  - Catastrophic Expense Health Insurance Study, January 27, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1348)
  - Syndicated Gambling in New York State, February 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1349)
  - Education Law Amendment, February 21, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1350)
  - Study of Emergency Housing Rent Control Law, February 24, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1351)
  - Simplifying a Complex Constitution, New York State Constitution, February 27, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1352)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, February-March 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1353)
  - Delinquent Real Estate Taxes in Albany County, March 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1354)
  - Financial Program for the Long Island Railroad, March 6, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1355)
  - State University of New York Master Plan, April 9, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1356)
  - Governor's Council on Rehabilitation, Interim Report, July 3, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1357)
  - Seymour Special Unit: Waste & Corruption in New York City, September 11, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1358)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee re: New Haven Railroad, Interim Report, October 30, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1359)
  - Investigation of Bingo in New York State, December 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1360)
  - Nuclear Port Survey of New York State, December 8, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1361)
  - Nuclear Port Survey of New York State, December 8, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1362)
  - Summary of Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 1363)
  - Hudson & Manhattan World Trade Center Project, January 29, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1364)
  - Governor's Council on Rehabilitation, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1365)
    Annual Report, February 9, 1962
  - Study of Needs for Sewage Works, Preliminary Report, February 16, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1366)
  - Medical Assistance for the Aged, March 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1367)
  - Bingo Control Inquiry, March 1, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1368)
  - Bingo Control Inquiry, March 1, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1369)
  - Bingo Control Inquiry, March 1, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1370)
  - Report on Railroad Tax Relief, March 1, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1371)
    Not Released
  - Thoroughbred Racing Report, March 16, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1372)
  - Diefendorf Report on School Financing, Interim Report, March 22, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1373)
  - Diefendorf Report on School Financing, Interim Report, March 22, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1374)
  - Kid Parent Match Report, March 26, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1375)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee, 2nd Interim Report & Study Prospectus, March 2, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1376)
  - Television & Higher Education, September 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1377)
  - Rockefeller Republican Record, September 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1378)
  - Survey of Middle-Income & Low Rent Housing Need & Demand in Albany, November 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1379)
  - New York Telephone Boiler Explosion Catastrophe, Preliminary Report, November 3, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1380)
  - New York Republican State Committee: The New York Report, December 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1381)
  - Office of Transportation, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1382)
    Annual Report, December, 1962
  - New York State Liquor Authority, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1383)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Status Report, December 19, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1384)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee Status Report, December 19, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1385)
  - Review of Workmen's Compensation in New York State, December 19, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1386)
  - Bingo Control Commission, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1387)
    Annual Report, December 31, 1962
  - New York State Police, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1388)
  - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 1389)
  - State Housing Rent Commission, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1390)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1391)
  - Report on Capital Harbor, Albany, January 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1392)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) Board of Trustees Report re: Tuition, January 22, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1393)
  - State Commission of Investigations Recommendations re: Syracuse Police Department, January 31, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1394)
  - Moreland Act Commission Report re: Public Welfare, February 4, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1395)
  - Moreland Act Commission Report re: Public Welfare, February 4, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1396)
  - Harness Racing Commission, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1397)
    Annual Report, February 4, 1963
  - New Haven Railroad Report, February 15, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1398)
  - Temporary Commission on Per Capita Aid, 1st Report, March 1, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1399)
  - Unemployment Insurance Financing in New York State, March 26, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1400)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee, 3rd Interim Report, May 10, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1401)
  - Tri-State Transportation Committee: Railroad Suburban Equipment Study, Status Report, May 22, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1402)
  - New York State Comptroller's Report, May 29, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1403)
  - Education for the Health Professions, June 19, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1404)
  - Muir Committee on Medical Education, July 2, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1405)
  - Muir Committee on Medical Education, July 2, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1406)
  - School Dropout Problem, Syracuse, July 24, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1407)
  - Standard Plans for School Construction, August 20, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1408)
  - Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Interim Report, September 3, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1409)
  - Moreland Commission, Study Paper 1, October 18, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1410)
  - Moreland Commission, Study Papers 2 & 3, October 21, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1411)
  - Moreland Commission, Study Paper 4, October 27, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1412)
  - Moreland Commission, Study Paper 5, October 28, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1413)
  - New York State Identification & Intelligence System, Feasibility Report & Recommendations, November 1, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1414)
  - Delaware River Basin Commission, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1415)
    Annual Report, December, 1963
  - Committee to Accelerate Middle-Income Housing & Urban Renewal Construction in New York City, December 26, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1416)
  - Off-Track Betting in England: A Pattern for New York, December 27, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1417)
  - Land Acquisition for Parks & Recreation, 2 Year Progress Report, January 21, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1418)
  - Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report & Recommendation 1, January 6, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1419)
  - Moreland Commission, Report & Recommendation 2, January 9, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1420)
  - Moreland Commission, Report & Recommendation 3, January 21, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1421)
  - Review & Appraisal of New York State's Low Income Housing, January 27, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1422)
  - Review & Appraisal of New York State's Low Income Housing, January 27, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1423)
  - New York State Racing Commission, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1424)
    Annual Report, January 29, 1964
  - State Advisory Council on Employment & Unemployment Insurance, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1425)
    Annual Report, January 31, 1964
  - Temporary Commission of Investigation, 6th Annual Report, March; 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1426)
  - New York State Racing Association Report, March 9, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1427)
  - Special Committee on Ethics, March 10, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1428)